♪ On A Far Off Planet
By Rene Aubry ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
By a loobular lake.
on a far-off planet.
there lived a young Smed.
and her name was Janet.
Huh? Ha-ha-ha! Weeeee!
Argh!
Not far away. on a humplety hill.
there lived a young Smoo
by the name of Bill.
Hmm.
Ha!
Haha!
Oh!
Huh! Mm.
Uff! Huh.
Aaaargh!
Huh!
Hmph!
Janet. like all the Smeds. was red.
and this is what
her grandfather said.
Never. never play with the... Smoos!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
They sleep in holes.
they wear strange shoes.
They jump about like... Kangaroos!
Never. never...
..play with the Smoos.
Ahem!
Bill. like the other Smoos.
was blue.
and these were the words
of Grandmother Smoo.
Never. never play with the Smeds.
Upon their heads.
They sleep in funny things
called beds.
Never. never play...
..with the Smeds.
Oh.
The Smeds. on their lake.
liked nothing better
than splashing about.
getting wetter and wetter.
Argh!
But Janet grew bored
of this watery play.
And that was the
reason...
..she tiptoed away.
The Smoos jumped about
on their humplety hill.
They bounced up and down it
and never stood still.
But Bill was beginning to think...
This is boring.
And that was the reason
he set off exploring.
Ah.
Oh.
Grrr.
Grrrr! Grrrr!
Eeee! Ah.
Janet met Bill in the Wurpular Wood.
where the trockles grew tall
and the glompoms smelled good.
Oh!
The two rubbed antennae
and played all day long.
I told you a story.
You sing me a song.
Hey!
Then they climbed to the top
of a jerberrycoot
and nibbled its juicy
and jellyful fruit.
Whoa! He!
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha!
He-he-he-he-he!
Ah.
Till who should disturb them
but Grandfather Smed.
shaking his fist
as he angrily said...
Never. never play with a Smoo.
Argh!
Oh! Ow!
For the hundredth time I say to you.
never. never play with a Smoo.
Grandmother Smoo was close behind.
and this is how she spoke her mind.
Ow! Never. never play with a Smed.
They're such a dreadful
<font color="
I'll say again
what I've always said -
never. never play with a Smed.
Years went by on the far-off planet.
Janet missed Bill...
..and Bill missed Janet.
So. off they crept.
whenever they could.
to sing and play
in the Wurpular Wood.
♪ Dream Of The Smeds And Dream
Of The Smoos By Rene Aubry ♪
Mmm!
Oh!
Huh!
Hello. everyone.
We've decided to wed.
But what do you think
their grandparents said?
Never. never marry a Smoo!
They're a beastly bunch.
They drink black tea.
They eat green stew.
Oh.
Never. never marry a Smoo.
One...
Never. never marry a Smed.
My dearest child.
are you off your head?
They eat brown bread.
Never. never marry a Smed.
Hmm.
Janet and Bill stole out that night.
while their family slept
and the squoon shone bright.
They clambered up
to the Smeds' red rocket.
Whoa!
Grandfather Smed has forgotten
<font color="
Bill pressed the button...
..and Janet steered.
When their families woke...
..they had both disappeared.
Argh!
The Smeds said...
Your Bill must have stolen
our Janet.
And taken her off
to a distant planet.
The Smoos said...
And lured him away
from the humplety hill.
Haha!
The Smoos climbed
into their rocket of blue.
Hmm... Mm-hm.
But what about us?
Hmm.
You had better come. too.
Mm.
Uh. uh.
Aaaaargh!
Huh?
Aaaaargh! Phew!
Suspicious and scowling.
they soared into space...
..till they reached Planet Vumjum...
..a dry. dusty place.
Huh!
Haha!
The Vums had long arms.
which they waved in the air...
..but they didn't have news
of the runaway pair.
Aaaaargh!
Ah! Oh!
The next stop was Lurglestrop.
covered in roses...
Ah-ha-choo!
Ooh! Oh!
..and watered by beasts
with small eyes and long noses.
Ooo-ooh!
Haha!
Ah-ha-haaaa...
..choo!
Hm. Oh.
They touched down on Grimbletosh...
..coated in grime.
Eeeeeugh!
They searched Planet Glurch
but found nothing but slime.
Uh.
Hmm.
Huh? Huh? Aaaaaargh!
Argh! Aaaargh!
Ugh!
Phew!
Ahem.
There is. One...
I'm sorry to tell you
we've run out of tea.
Oh.
Hey.
Have some of our milk.
Oh! Ha-ha!
Ahem.
Ah!
Huh?
Then Grandfather Smed said...
My hair needs a trim.
And Grandmother Smoo
kindly cut it for him.
They landed on Scloop.
where the Scloopies wore kilts.
They flew to Klaboo.
where the Klabs walked on stilts.
Oh. Oh.
Aaaaaargh! Aaaaargh! Oh!
We've searched all year long.
And we'll search longer still.
Huh!
We didn't find Janet.
Alas...
..said the Smoos.
and the Smeds said... Alack!
We have failed in our quest.
We had better turn back.
So. they turned and flew home
to their very own planet.
Hm?
Huh?
And far down below them. they saw...
Bill and Janet!
Huh?
Whoa!
The rocket touched down.
and they ran to the wood
where the trockles grew tall
and the glompoms smelled good.
And there. in a glade.
by the rocket of red.
were the runaway Smoo
and the runaway Smed.
We got lost and flew home again.
had left us behind.
Ah.
Oh. Argh!
There was joy. jam and jumping.
Then Janet said...
Maybe you'd like to make friends
with our dear little baby.
A baby!
But no.
That baby was purple
from head to toe.
Ah. Oh. Who's a bub-bub?
They all hugged the Smoo-Smed.
Our new baby brother!
And Grandpa and Gran even
hugged one another.
Oh-ha-ha-ha! Oh!
Ah.
They laughed and they splashed
and they danced with delight.
and they played with that baby
from morning till night.
We've made him a rattle.
We've made him a flute.
Let's feed him the fruit
of the jerberrycoot!
And they sang by the light
of the silvery squoon.
And you can sing. too.
Play with the Smeds.
And play with the Smoos.
Play with whichever friends
you choose.
Then close your eyes.
and while you snooze...
Dream of the Smeds.
And dream of the Smoos.
♪ Dream Of The Smeds And Dream
Of The Smoos By Rene Aubry ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today